Guide to the George Nicolau Papers WAG.250
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory, 1
  - Whitney Blake Co. / United Electrical, Radio, & Machine Workers of America (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - IATSE / WOR Division of RKO-General (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - AFGE Local C-111 / U.S. Customs (FMCS 76K 19403) (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - West Orange NJ Teachers (72 92D) (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Western Publishing / Local 274, Graphic Communications International Union (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - WPIX / Local 1212, IBEW (9295-6; Holiday Pay) (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - US Food Service / IBTL Local 559 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - USWA Local 285 / Armstrong World Industries (610 01) (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Yonkers Bd. Of Ed. / Yonkers Fed. of Teachers (general) (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Yonkers Federation of Teachers and Yonkers Bd. of Ed. (re: assignment of double classes) (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Yonkers Fed of Teachers / Yonkers Bd. of Ed. (S. Kotler) (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Yonkers Fed. Of Teachers / Yonkers Bd. of Ed. (Linton & Chapman) (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Yonkers Fed. of Teachers / Yonkers Bd. of Ed (More Effective Schools Program) (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Yonkers Fed of Teachers / Yonkers Bd. of Ed (C. Reale) (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Yonkers Fed. of Teachers / Yonkers Bd. of Ed (Sabbatical Leaves) (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Yonkers Fed. of Teachers / Yonkers Bd. of Ed. (Sabbatical Leaves 1976 77) (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Younkers Fed. of Teachers / Younkers Board of Ed (use of school aide as teacher) (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Zionist Organization of America / D. C. 1707, Community and Social Agency Employees Union, AFSCME (1249-88) (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - NABET, Local 31 / NBC (1630-0022-75) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - NABET, AFL-CIO, CLC / NBC (Grievance #NW-74-1) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NABET, Local 31 / NBC (Grievance Number NW 74-14) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NABET / NBC (Recording by W. Hall for Update) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NABET, AFL-CIO, CLC / NBC (Transfer of Work NW 74-16) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NBC / NABET (Grievance Number NW 75-14) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - NBC / NABET (Gr. No. NW 75-33) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NABET NBC (NW 75-56) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 76-27) Videotape Eds, - Meal Periods) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 76-32; Permanent Upgrading-Radio) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 76-34; Anniversary Raise C. Conway) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 76-39; Payback Day Requests) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 76-41; Violations of NW 75-12) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 76-48; Chiron Upgrading) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NBC / NABET (NW 76-60; R. McKay Improper Seniority) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - NBC / NABET (NW 77-12; Chenevert II) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 78-47) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 78-47R) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 78-52) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 79-8; NW 78-5) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - NBC / NABET (NW 79-14) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 79-38) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 79-17) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 80-8) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 80-7) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - NABET /NBC (NW 80-12) (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 80-16 (Taylor) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 80-24) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 80-26) (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 80-35) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 81-1) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 81-2) (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 81-4) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 81-6; Schindler) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 81-21 & 22; Ross and Batton) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - NABET / NBC (NW81-26) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 81-27) (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 81-61) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 82-16) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 82-28) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 82-34; Lopez) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 85-17) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 85-21) (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 85-76 & 77) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - NABET / NBC (NW 86-106) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - NABET / NBC (NWM 77-1) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - NABET / NBC (NWA 78-1) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - NABET / NBC (NWM 80-1 and NWA 80-3) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - NABET / NBC (NWM 80-2) (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - NABET / NBC (NWA 80-1) (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - NABET / NBC (NWM 81-2) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - ABC / DGA (35-80; Washington Radio Practice) (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - ABC / DGA (6:564; KTNV, WXYZ) (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - ABC / DGA (Selchert) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - ABC / DGA (Steinmetz) (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - CBS / DGA (D. Bona) (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - CBS / DGA (6 CBS 534; Sports Directors and Associate Directors) (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - NBC / DGA (Eric Bell) (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - NBC / DGA (Disco suspension) (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - NBC / DGA (Disciplinary Memo) (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - NBC / DGA (Gulf War Parade; 91 NBC 873) (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - NBC / DGA (First Class Travel) (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - NBC/ DGA (Promos) (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - NBC / DGA (Sunday Today) (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - NBC / DGA (minicams) (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - NBC / DGA (7:647 Night News Graphics) (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - NBC / DGA (Gary Weis) (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - NBC / DGA (minicam 7 NBC 723) (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - DGA / Illustra Films (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - DGA / Rothberg (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - ABC / WGA (Barry) (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - WGA / ABC (1419 92; Lubart) (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - WGA / ABC (1231 81 newswriters) (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - WGA / York Enterprises (David Axlerod) (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - WGA / CBS (0962; 81Busch and Hicks) (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - WGA, East / CBS (Editors fees) (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - WGA / CSB (1583 82; Newswriter Workload) (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - WGA, East / CBS (Lane Vernardos Case) (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - WGA / CBS (Discharge of Roger Feinman) (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - WGA / Gaberock Enterprises (Price and Antonacchi) (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - WGA / Manhattan Entertainment (Malko) (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - WGA / Tilos Productions (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - L. 144, Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home and Allied Health Services Union / Brookhaven (Simmons Discharge) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - SNY / L. 144 (Brookhaven; Ellis) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - L. 144 / Cobble Hill (Barthelemy) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Fieldston / L. 144 (Lateness Policy) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Franklin / L. 144 (Eve St. Juste) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Franklin / L. 144 (Vado) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - SNY / L. 144 (Williamsbridge / Wiggan) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - SNY / L. 144 (Shoreview; Grospe) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle Home for the Aged (Gonzalez) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Clearview / L. 144 (S. Young) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Altshuler) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Altshuler termination) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - L. 144 / Beth Israel (355 97; Carter) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Beckford) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Roberta Best) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Jack Crocitto) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (10 % Differential) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - L. 144, SEIU / Brooklyn Hospital (Free Parking Rights) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Francis Ellington) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (L. Friedman) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Friedman Suspension) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Discharge of F. Gonzales) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Guy) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Lindsey) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Goldie Hoffman) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Holiday Pay / Call-In Pay) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Hollar) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Jones) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Johnstone) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Malcolm) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Newman) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Newman) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Workmens Circle / L. 144 (H. Ortiz) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Richards) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Workmens Circle / L. 144 (RN In-charge Pay) (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Antonio Rodriguez) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Roman Suspension) (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (W. Stewart) (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Valdez) (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - L. 144 / Village (Willis) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Enrique Vega) (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Whitfield I) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Whitfield II) (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Workmens Circle / L. 144 (Whitfield III) (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - L. 144 / Workmens Circle (Woldeguiorguis) (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - D.C. 37 / Board of Ed. (Ackrish) (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - D.C. 37 / Bd. of Ed. (Bureau of School Supplies) (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (School Aides Evander Childs and Forest Hills) (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - D.C. 37 / NYC Board of Ed (Norah DeRespiris) (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (Doran and Stephens) (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - D.C. 37 / Board of Ed (E. Gleich) (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - D.C. 37 / NYC Board of Ed (Hannah Goldman) (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (Hamilton) (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - D.C. 37 / Board of Ed (Harren High) (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (Hourly School Lunch Workers) (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (Julian) (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (School Aide Sophie Kevelson; Walton High School) (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (Lucchini) (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (School Aide JHS 189 Mrs. Esther Kriedman) (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (Maxwell) (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - DC 37 / NYC Board of Ed (Douglas Moore) (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - DC 37 / NYC Board of Ed (Mohamed Moussa) (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - DC 37 / NYC Board of Ed (Elizabeth Patterson) (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - DC 37 / NYC Board of Ed (Motor Vehicle Operators, BSL) (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (Wooten, et al) (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (Elizabeth Patterson) (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (Scott) (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - DC 37 / NYC Board of Ed (SPARK Program) (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (School Aides Francis Lewis) (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - DC 37 / NYC Board of Ed (James Purvis) (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - DC 37 / Board of Ed (School Neighborhood Workers 35 Hour Week) (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - NABET/ABC AIO 80-1 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - NABET/ABC AIO 80-2 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - NABET/ABC AIO 83-1 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - NABET/ABC AIO 84-1 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - NABET/ABC AIO 84-2 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - NABET/ABC AIO 85-1 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - NABET/ABC ARW 77-5 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - NABET/ABC ARW 78-9 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - NABET/ABC ARW 78-10 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - NABET/ABC ARW 78-11 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - NABET/ABC ARW 78-14 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - NABET/ABC ARW 78-15 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - NABET/ABC ARW (Arbitrability 1979) (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - NABET/ABC ARW 79-7 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - NABET/ABC ARW 79-9 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - NABET/ABC ARW 80-1 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - NABET/ABC ARW 80-5 & 6 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - NABET/ABC ARW 81-4 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - NABET/ABC ARW 81-8 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - NABET/ABC AWA 78-1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - NABET/ABC AWA 79-2 / AWM 79-2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - NABET/ABC AWA 79-3 / AWM 79-1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - NABET/ABC AWA 80-3 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - NABET/ABC AW 75-33 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - NABET/ABC AW 76-6 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - NABET/ABC AW 76-17 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - NABET/ABC AW 76-203 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - NABET/ABC AW 77-11 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - NABET/ABC AW 77-32 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - NABET/ABC AW 77-35 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - NABET/ABC AW 77-36 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - NABET/ABC AW 78-1 (Ciraci and Perry) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - NABET/ABC AW 78-20 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - NABET/ABC AW 78-21 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - NABET/ABC AW 78-23 (TD Assignment) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - NABET/ABC AW 78-28 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - NABET/ABC AW 78-38 (Unilateral Audio by Non-NABETs) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - NABET/ABC AW 79-7 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - NABET/ABC AW 79-13 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - NABET/ABC AW 79-14 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - NABET/ABC AW 79-19 (Gruiff) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - NABET/ABC AW 79-22 (Microphone Clamps) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - NABET/ABC AW 79-27 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - NABET/ABC AW 79-31 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - NABET/ABC AW 79-34 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - NABET/ABC AW 79-37 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - NABET/ABC AW 79-43 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - NABET/ABC AW 79-44 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - NABET/ABC AW 79-45 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - NABET/ABC AW 80-3 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - NABET/ABC AW 80-13 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - NABET/ABC AW 80-14 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - NABET/ABC AW 80-15 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - NABET/ABC AW 80-16 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - NABET/ABC AW 80-18 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - NABET/ABC AW 80-30 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - NABET/ABC AW 80-39 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - NABET/ABC AW 81-10 (20.10) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - NABET/ABC AW 81-27 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - NABET/ABC AW 81-64 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - NABET/ABC AW 81-42 (Hoover) (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - NABET/ABC AW 81-45 (Champion) (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - NABET/ABC AW 81-59 (20.10) (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - NABET/ABC AW 81-61 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - NABET/ABC AW 81-63 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - NABET/ABC AW 82-6 (20.10) (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - NABET/ABC AW 82-11 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - NABET/ABC AW 82-3 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - NABET/ABC AW 82-5 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - NABET/ABC AW 83-4 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - NABET/ABC AW 83-7 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - NABET/ABC AW 83-8 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - NABET/ABC AW 83-10 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - NABET/ABC AW 83-13 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - NABET/ABC AW 83-13 (20.10) (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - NABET/ABC AW 83-19 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - NABET/ABC AW 84-8 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - NABET/ABC AW 84-12 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - NABET/ABC AW 84-9 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - NABET/ABC AW 85-10 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - NABET/ABC AW 85-11 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - NABET/ABC AW 85-24 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - NABET/ABC AW 86-1 (20.10) (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - NABET/ABC AC 75-58 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - NABET/ABC AC 76-49 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - NABET/ABC AC 77-26 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - NABET/ABC AC 78-2 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - NABET/ABC AC 78-6 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - NABET/ABC AC 78-27 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - NABET/ABC AC 78-33 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - NABET/ABC AC 79-35 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - NABET/ABC AC 80-39 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - NABET/ABC AC 81-3 & 4 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - NABET/ABC AC 34 & 35 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - NABET/ABC AC 82-8 (Johnson) (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - NABET/ABC AC 82-28 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - NABET/ABC AC 82-66 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - NABET/ABC AC 82-62 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - NABET/ABC AC 82-68 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - NABET/ABC AC 83-4 & 5 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - NABET/ABC AC 83-7 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - NABET/ABC AC 83-37 (20.10) (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - NABET/ABC AC 83-87 (Hale) (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - NABET/ABC AC 84-8 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - NABET/ABC AC 84-26 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - NABET/ABC AC 84-50, 52, 57, 59 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - NABET/ABC AC 84-86 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - NABET/ABC AC 84-90 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - NABET/ABC AC 84-104 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - NABET/ABC AC 84 (Baumgart) (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - NABET/ABC AC 84-93 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - NABET/ABC AC 85-12 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - NABET/ABC AC 85-67 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - NABET/ABC AC 85-73 (Klingman) (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - NABET/ABC AC 86-13 (Kolarik) (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - NABET/ABC AC 86-25 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - NABET/ABC AH 84-120 (20.10) (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - NABET/ABC AH 85-72 & 73 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Air Canada / Connectors (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Aero Mexico / IAM (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Air India / IBT, L. 732 (Staab) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Allied Pilots Association / Flagship Airlines (Al-Wardi) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Alaska Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - AFA / Atlantic Coast Airlines (Robertson) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Alaska Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (737-900) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - American Airlines / APA (2000) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - American Eagle / ALPA (Interest Arbitration) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - American Eagle / AFA (Susan Daniels) AFA 22-52-1-111-02 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - American Eagle / AFA (Equipment Substitution) 22-99-02-34-99 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - American Eagle / AFA (22-99-02-02-01) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - American Eagle / ALPA (Vijzelman; 121-1102) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - American Eagle / ALPA (Training Freeze; MEC No. 2402) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - American Eagle / ALPA (Bulletin Board; MEC 1902 & 2202) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - American Eagle / AFA (Leon; AFA 22-49-01-02-04) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Continental Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (03-20; Bousquet) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Continental Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Holmberg 02-12) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Continental Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Ferry Flights 03-04) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Continental Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (Plummer; 02-03) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Continental Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (CRAF; 03-02) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Continental / Frontier (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Continental / International Association of Machinists (Flight Attendant) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Continental / IBT (Martinez Per Diem Pay) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Continental / IBT (0418 Group) (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Continental / IBT (0456; Super Tug) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Eagle Electronic / Local 365, UAW (01567 90) (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Delta / Air Line Pilots Association (ALT 02-39; Lake) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Express Jet / ALPA (Cocchiola) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Federal Express / Flying Tigers Award (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Federal Express / Flying Tigers (Dispute Resolution Committee) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Federal Express / Flying Tigers (Dispute Resolution Committee; Dilbeck) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Federal Express / Flying Tigers (The Broader Issue) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Federal Express / Flying Tigers (B747 Vacancies LAX) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Frontier / CWA (2316-03 & 2321-03; Temporary Employees) (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Horizon / Association of Flight Attendants (06-17-2-08-01; Agency Stop) (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Mesaba Aviation / Aircraft Mechanics Fraternal Association (Kingery) (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Northwest / Air Line Pilots Association (Sutton) (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - NWA / Pre-Merger Republic Pilots (92-111; monthly bidding) (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - NWA / Pre-Merger Republic Pilots (92-104; Insufficient Bidders) (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - NWA / International Association of Machinists (CSA Gate Screening) (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - NWA / Air Line Pilots Association (2604-02; Hickman) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - NWA / IBT (02-223 & 02-226, force majeure) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - NWA / Republic of Airlines Pilot Merger Representatives (03-160; Replacement Aircraft) (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - NWA / Republic of Airlines Pilot Merger Representatives (03-162) (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association (Denial of Awarded Patterns) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association (NY-158-84) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association and Flight Engineers International Association (Med./ Arb.) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association (NY-135-83) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association (NY-233-83) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association (NY-77-84) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association (NY-46-84) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Pan American World Airways (Proffer I) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Pan American World Airways (Proffer II) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Pan American World Airways (Proffer III) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Pan American World Airways (Gn IV) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Pan American World Airways (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Piedmont / Association of Flight Attendants (3/18/05) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Republic Airlines / Air Line Pilot Association (RC-MEC-85-9) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Republic Airlines / Air Line Pilot Association (PHX-83-1) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Spirit Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants-CWA (39-99-02-10-03; Sick/ Late Policy) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - PAN AM / Flight Engineers International Association (Irwin S. Astor) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - PAN AM / Flight Engineers International Association (George Kanakis Dunn Case) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - PAN AM / Flight Engineers International Association (Discharge) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - PAN AM / Flight Engineers International Association (R.B. Rhodes-Duty time limits) (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - PAN AM / Flight Engineers International Association (Summary Ruling) (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - PAN AM / Flight Engineers International Association (Air Vietnam) (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - PAN AM / Independent Union of Flight Attendants (Nadale / Halkides) (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - PAN AM / Independent Union of Flight Attendants (FS-80-83-SFO) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - PAN AM / Independent Union of Flight Attendants (FS-80-174-JFK) (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - PAN AM / Independent Union of Flight Attendants (FS-81-76-JFK) (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Tower Air / Association of Flight Attendants (Wenger) (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - TWA / International Association of Machinists (Four Hour Rule) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (NY-59-86; Barter) (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (Anderson) (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (Brown) (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (A-Plan) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (Jakab) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (Meland / Weitzel) (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (Pay Date; TWA 22-89) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (Carl Straub) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (Dent; 85-678) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (Fekete; 83-869 & 82-878) (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (Fekete II; 87-154) (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (LaPollo) (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (84-0241) (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (84-0241 remedy) (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (Pluister) (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (86-182; Rose) (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (Yanusz; 87-014) (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - TWA / International Association of Machinists (Alicea) (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - TWA / International Association of Machinists (Culberson) (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - TWA / International Association of Machinists (Dunlap/ Lancioni) (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - TWA / International Association of Machinists (Grecia) (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - TWA / International Association of Machinists (Madison) (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - TWA / International Association of Machinists (Malatesta) (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - TWA / International Association of Machinists (Vigilante-JFK) (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - TWA / International Association of Machinists (Williams TW-JFK-11-8) (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - TWA / Ozark Airlines (Baldwin) (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - TWA / Ozark Airlines (1988 Ozark Captain Protective Cell) (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (6-92; Air Wisconsin) (Box 10, Folder 1)